<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Demo Site</title>
    <link>https://odhyp.github.io/demo/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Demo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo 0.125.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 06:00:00 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://odhyp.github.io/demo/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Check out your competition</title>
      <link>https://odhyp.github.io/demo/posts/post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 06:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://odhyp.github.io/demo/posts/post-3/</guid>
      <description>What better way to draw inspiration than to look at your well-established competition?&#xA;It’s worth taking a look at popular, highly reviewed blogs because their strategy and execution is what got them to grow in credibility. The purpose of doing this isn’t to copy these elements, but to gain better insight into what readers appreciate in a quality blog.&#xA;When you find a competitor’s blog, take the following steps:&#xA;Determine whether they’re actually a direct competitor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand your audience</title>
      <link>https://odhyp.github.io/demo/posts/post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 06:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://odhyp.github.io/demo/posts/post-2/</guid>
      <description>Before you start writing your blog post, make sure you have a clear understanding of your target audience. To do so, take the following steps.&#xA;Ask yourself exploratory questions To discover your audience, ask questions like: Who are they? Are they like me, or do I know someone like them? What do they want to know about? What will resonate with them?&#xA;Jot down your notes in a notepad or a document.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Start a Blog</title>
      <link>https://odhyp.github.io/demo/posts/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 06:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://odhyp.github.io/demo/posts/post-1/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve ever read a blog post, you’ve consumed content from a thought leader that is an expert in their industry. Chances are if the blog post was written effectively, you came away with helpful knowledge and a positive opinion about the writer or brand that produced the content.&#xA;Anyone can connect with their audience through blogging and enjoy the myriad benefits that blogging provides: organic traffic from search engines, promotional content for social media, and recognition from a new audience you haven’t tapped into yet.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
